Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
♪Let the daylight
pierce through the night♪
♪Unveiling the dazzling galaxy♪
♪This scorched remnant of myself♪
♪In this world of capricious tides♪
♪That perfect warmth♪
♪You are my only star♪
♪Heartless, obsessed, hopeful, loathing♪
♪How can we escape the regretful pasts♪
♪Watch the sky plunge into the sea♪
♪As dawn's first light
sketches the sky's outline♪
♪Entwined between our fingertips♪
♪When destiny weaves a brilliant net♪
♪Our souls are forged from the shards♪
=Flying Up Without Disturb=
=Episode 1=
(This is Lingyou Realm,)
(Lingyou Realm)
(where cultivators reside.)
(All cultivators)
(dream of)
(ascension.)
(But as for me,)
(I don't even have a spiritual root,)
(let alone ascending.)
(My name is Kong Hou.)
(I believe that once I earn)
(enough spirit stones
for a spiritual tool,)
(I'll surely become)
(a true cultivator, too.)
(Don't you think)
(this dress)
(looks nice?)
Come on.
This dress
costs only 19 spirit stones now.
That's right.
Just 19 spirit stones
and this beautiful Fairy Dress
can be yours to take home.
Who wants one?
Raise your hands.
We barely made
any money.
(Ling Hui, Yunhua Sect)
You still can't
afford a spiritual tool.
I came prepared.
(Liuguang Sect)
Isn't it...
This bracelet may be precious,
but
it's useless to me.
Better sell it
for money.
Good for you.
Please take a look.
This bracelet
is no ordinary accessory.
Look.
This bracelet was once
worn by our top cultivator
in the Lingyou Realm,
Master Zhong Xi.
Everybody knows Master Zhong Xi, right?
He's the top cultivator
who led Liuguang Sect's
Luanfeng Peak disciples
to subdue the Eight Corpse Kings
of Mount Beigu.
His fame echoes throughout
Lingyou Realm.
This very bracelet
was once...
How dare you block
our Elder's path?
Enough.
Don't frighten the commoners.
(Nascent Soul Elder, Yuxiao Sect)
(What happened?)
(What are they looking at?)
She's the bossy
Nascent Soul Elder
of the Yuxiao Sect.
Useless.
My reputation
is ruined because of you.
Is she going to
abduct this man in broad daylight?
Pretty boy.
Nice figure.
Did you stop my sedan chair
to admire my beauty?
Did I
startle you?
You're blocking the way.
Let me buy you a drink
to make amends.
Senior.
Please keep a distance.
Pretty girl.
You want to meddle with us?
Yeah, so what?
Very well.
Excellent.
But I wonder
if you can handle this.
It doesn't matter if I can handle this.
My master
certainly can manage you.
Who's your master?
Master Wang Tong.
She's the disciple
of Master Wang Tong.
The Yunhua Sect
can teach the Elder a lesson.
You look like
a minor rogue cultivator.
How dare you talk big
to me?
Are you suicidal?
Actually,
I lack the spiritual energy
to fight her.
I'll count to three.
Then we run.
Understand?
Without a fight?
Why should we fight when we can run?
How dare you
try to snatch a man from my hands?
Three. Run!
You...
Get them.
- Hurry.
You're so good-looking.
They didn't hurt you, right?
Are you injured?
No.
Thankfully.
Check over there.
Hurry up.
(W-What's happening?)
(Spiritual energy is pouring in.)
(How did this happen?)
(So much spiritual energy. Amazing.)
Don't move.
If someone finds us here,
we'll be in trouble.
(How is this possible?)
Let go.
What are you doing?
I wasn't doing anything.
I was just
trying to protect you.
Why did you let go?
Hold on a bit longer.
We should keep a distance.
Please maintain some propriety.
After all,
I saved your life.
Why can't I hold your hands for a bit?
You're no different
from that person now.
There...
There is a huge difference.
That Nascent Soul Elder
was trying to abduct you in public
and take liberties with you.
I...
Weren't you doing
the exact same thing?
True.
Right,
you don't look like
you're from Yong City.
Are you here for fun?
Senior Ling Hui.
It's her messenger talisman.
I sent her to get help.
Stay close. Don't get lost.
I have questions for you.
Let's go.
- Stop.
- Over there. Hurry.
Pretty boy.
There you are again.
Seeing you
makes me so happy.
We're surrounded.
There's no escape.
You brat. Calling reinforcements again?
This time,
you won't be so lucky.
Interesting.
How interesting.
I didn't expect that
you're not just handsome,
but also quite skilled.
Taking you down
doesn't require any real skill.
The Yunhua Sect, indeed.
Senior Tan, forget it.
Better not chase them.
Lucky she ran fast.
(Tan Feng, Head Disciple of Yunhua Sect's Louyue Peak)
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
He helped me earlier.
Are you alright?
It was so dangerous.
I didn't know you were so powerful.
You lack spiritual energy.
What else could I do?
Kong Hou.
This is...?
I'm from the Liuguang Sect.
A master from the Liuguang Sect.
Kong Hou.
You sneaked out again.
If Master finds out,
we'll all be in trouble.
Let's go back.
Thank you for saving her.
We have matters to attend to
back in our sect.
Wait.
Didn't you have
something to say?
Yeah, Senior Tan.
I haven't even thanked him properly.
Don't worry. It's fine.
Just a few words with him.
Master won't find out.
There is so much more
I want to ask you about.
Let me think...
Jingxin Bookshop.
Wait for me there.
(Jingxin Bookshop)
Young master.
Coming through.
I was away for a second,
and you were gone.
Why are you here?
(Lin Hu, Liuguang Sect)
(Jingxin Bookshop)
Jingxin Bookshop.
Why are we here?
Aren't we tracking down
that dark cultivator?
I'm waiting for someone.
Who?
Who's worth the wait?
Gentlemen.
Looking for books?
The Master Writer.
Sorry, young master.
No one has bought those books
for a long time now.
So
I stopped stocking them ages ago.
Why don't you
check the other books?
No need.
You don't even have a spiritual root.
What if you run into
dark cultivators out there?
I have to put you
under detention this time.
How come there's a barrier?
Heading out, Kong Hou?
I...
I just wanted to
stroll around the courtyard.
It's too stuffy in the room.
I just want some fresh air.
You're under detention.
I know exactly
what you're up to.
Sneaking out for fun again?
Stay put.
No more clever ideas.
Exactly.
Let's go.
(Jingxin Bookshop)
Young master.
It's so late now.
She's clearly not coming.
I promised her.
Sorry, gentlemen.
Could you come back tomorrow?
We're closing for the night.
You're closing?
Young master, t-they're closing.
Did something happen to her?
That person
boosted my spiritual energy.
I wonder if it works.
Let's see.
It actually worked.
(Master Wang Tong, Master of Yunhua Sect's Qiyue Peak)
What worked?
Master.
Master, you came back.
So you broke the barrier.
I thought
I had grown more powerful.
Who?
You, of course.
You got beaten up?
It wasn't that bad.
Come on.
I'll take you somewhere.
Where are we going?
To take revenge.
(Yuxiao Sect)
Master.
Aren't we taking revenge
on Nascent Soul Elder?
With my cultivation level,
ten of them wouldn't stand
a chance against me.
I can turn
a Nascent Soul master into a newbie.
But what if she cheats
or uses tricks?
That's why we're going for
a sneak attack.
Master.
What's wrong?
Wait for me.
Don't go anywhere.
I'll be right back.
Elder.
What?
We found the pretty boy.
You did?
He's at the Qingquan Inn.
"Pretty boy"?
Oh my.
I forgot about him.
(Master, I'm going to save someone.)
(Don't worry about me.)
I've finally found you.
Young master.
You...
I'm not here for you.
What brings you here?
I'm here for you.
What for?
Do you know
you're in grave danger?
No time to explain.
They're coming.
Come with me.
You're not in danger.
What? What danger?
What does she mean?
(Qingquan Inn)
Elder.
Where is he?
The innkeeper said they fled.
Find him.
I don't care
if you tear this place apart.
Where are we going?
- Over there.
You don't have to do anything.
Don't worry. I got this.
- Over there.
- Stop.
- Get them.
Oh no, they're all coming.
Let's go.
It's quite windy here.
Be careful.
Acting nice? What's your angle?
My angle?
I just feel bad that I stood you up
and want to make amends.
Sorry.
Something came up earlier.
Since you were busy,
let's forget it.
Right,
do you need to regulate your energy?
(Where does that come from?)
(She's acting)
(rather weirdly.)
Why should I do that?
Just do me a favor, okay?
Give me your hands.
Why do you need my hands?
The truth is,
I've been meaning to tell you.
I have no spiritual root.
No spiritual root?
Without a spiritual root,
I can't claim any spiritual tool,
let alone a chance of ascension.
That's why you acted that way before.
I also find it strange.
Whenever I make physical contact
with you,
the spiritual energy
comes rushing
into my system.
Then my spiritual energy surges.
I just want to
maintain contact with you.
Then I can
accumulate some spiritual energy.
But
I can't just take advantage of you.
Let's perform energy regulation.
I gain spiritual energy
and you
can regulate
your spiritual energy.
It's a win-win.
But
I think I'm too useless.
It only works
if I keep holding your hands.
Nonsense.
It does sound absurd,
but it's true.
All my years in the Lingyou Realm,
I've never heard of
such a thing.
Do you have
ulterior motives
and made up this excuse?
I...
You do look
kind of attractive,
but
I wouldn't go that far.
Kong Hou.
My disciple.
Where are you?
Your master?
Oh no.
He's definitely
going to drag me back.
Stop sneaking around. Go out there.
No.
I don't want to go back.
Please help me.
What's in it for me?
I don't care.
Let's go.
Kong Hou.
(It's already dawn.)
(Master must have returned.)
He's asleep.
Does that mean
I won't get caught?
What are you doing?
I...
I just...
Trying to regulate my energy
while I'm asleep?
Yeah, what's wrong?
It's a win-win
situation.
My spiritual energy
has increased a lot
thanks to you.
Maybe I'm as powerful
as you now.
You'd better
behave yourself.
Otherwise,
I'll take forceful measures.
Forceful measures?
Go ahead and try.
I...
You've got some nerve.
Just do me a favor.
Please.
Let me boost my spiritual energy.
No.
It would benefit
both of us.
Please.
No.
Young master.
What...
Why are you hugging?
Who are you?
None of your business.
You must be that girl
from the Yunhua Sect.
Well?
Young master, we have a lead.
Wait.
Let's think this through.
Are we really barging in?
Why not?
Let's calm down
and think about it.
There are only three of us.
How many of them are there?
At least 30.
Exactly.
Under such circumstances,
wouldn't it be wiser
to run away
than barge in?
We've been running all night.
That's right. Let's charge in.
Wait.
You transferred me spiritual energy.
Don't get into a fight now.
It's dangerous.
Are you saying that you can fight?
Well, I can't fight either.
So,
among the three of us,
only he can fight.
Will he make it?
What do you mean?
Looking down on me?
Or disrespecting the Luanfeng Peak.
Exactly.
Right.
Luanfeng Peak
is the top branch in the Liuguang Sect.
The Yuxiao Sect
must show some respect.
They're just
an affiliated organization
of your Liuguang Sect.
You remember now?
How did I forget that?
If I had remembered earlier,
I wouldn't have
dragged you around, hiding.
We don't need to be afraid of them.
Where's the pretty boy?
Where is he?
It's been an entire night.
You're all useless.
What's the point
of keeping you around?
Yunhua Sect.
How dare they
cross me like this?
They are not
showing respect.
They won't get away with this.
Yunhua Sect is here.
I was looking for you.
And you came on your own.
Wait.
What's wrong?
Got any final words
to say?
Do you know
who they are?
Pretty boy.
And a nobody.
Wrong.
They're the "authority" lineage.
No, the "orthodox" lineage.
Yeah.
The "orthodox" lineage.
The master and the supreme master
of Liuguang Sect's
Luanfeng Peak.
What a surprise.
My pretty boy is not just handsome
but also highly skilled.
You're an elite from the Luanfeng Peak.
I like you even more now.
Aren't you scared?
Why should I be scared?
Liuguang Sect
is our parent organization.
So I should be scared?
Don't be ridiculous.
Don't forget that
your Yuxiao Sect
relies entirely
on the Liuguang Sect's protection
to maintain its status as
Lingyou Realm's top merchant sect.
That's true.
But remember this, pretty boy.
The Yuxiao Sect
contributes massive wealth
to your Liuguang Sect every year.
Take that into consideration.
If you think
your offering to the Liuguang Sect
allows you to act recklessly
in Lingyou Realm,
then we don't need you
as an affiliated organization.
We will not
retain your offerings, either.
Such bold words, pretty boy.
I really like you.
But don't forget
that the Yuxiao and Liuguang Sects
shall never provoke each other.
Your head
said that himself.
Our head did say that.
So...
So even if
Master Zhong Xi himself
stood before me today,
he should show me due respect.
Who do you think you are?
You're insane.
Are you saying
that even if Master Zhong Xi
were present,
you still wouldn't be scared?
(Dragon's Roar Sword.)
(His sword)
(is so intimidating?)
I was wrong, Master.
This is a misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding?
I saw it with my own eyes.
Stop making excuses.
Step aside.
Lin Hu.
Walk her through it
and see
if we misunderstood her.
Got it.
Zhou Xing.
You're the sister
of Yuxiao Sect Leader Zhou Cang.
You've always been domineering
thanks to your connection.
Three months ago,
you bullied people
in your turf,
causing dozens of casualties.
Didn't you?
A-After
Zhou Cang sent you to Yong City,
you remained unchanged.
Exploiting local sects'
reluctance to intervene,
you plundered and oppressed
countless citizens.
You've done so much harm.
You're a real piece of work.
Real piece of work.
This is slander.
That's exaggerated.
Master, you must believe me.
I'm innocent.
Innocent?
How dare you say that?
Go on.
Look.
These are
the testimonies
from the victims.
Some
couldn't seek justice,
and nearly hung themselves.
It was consensual.
I didn't force anyone.
I swear they were happy about it.
A-And this.
Look.
Testimonies
from your fellow disciples.
Even they couldn't tolerate it.
Master,
I realize my mistakes.
For my brother's sake,
please spare me.
Please, I beg you.
Zhou Cang's sister
should be under 20
with no cultivation to speak of.
What's your deal?
Explain your spiritual energy.
C-Can I say it?
Confess.
I-I...
Stop stuttering.
Just say it.
I took pills.
Pills? She took pills?
What pills did you take?
Longgu Pills.
Longgu Pills?
Keep it down.
She took Longgu Pills.
You're quite something,
bullying people
and taking forbidden pills.
Where did you get the pills?
I-I bought those from Qing Yuan
in that Forbidden Forest
of your Yunhua Sect.
Qing...
(Yuxiao Sect)
This is weird.
What's wrong?
That Nascent Soul Elder
was all tough earlier.
Why did she back down the moment
you drew your sword?
That's because
he is Zhong...
Some people
only talk tough
and have no real skills.
That's nice.
You drew your sword.
All problems solved.
Poor me.
I just wanted a friend
to regulate some spiritual energy.
Someone
could easily help
a friend in need,
but he simply
refuses to lift a finger.
We're mere acquaintances,
hardly friends.
I'm off.
How can you
be so heartless?
Young master.
Should we look into the pills?
Wait for me over there.
What does it take
for you to help me?
I don't know how you absorb
spiritual energy.
But never take shortcuts
to gain cultivation.
Or there will be consequences.
I have things to do. Farewell.
It is weird that I can absorb
spiritual energy.
Never mind.
That Nascent Soul
said she bought the Longgu Pills
in the Forbidden Forest.
No way.
Senior Tan must
look into it.
(Yunhua Sect)
Senior Tan.
This is weird.
Where did he go?
Isn't it obvious?
He must be working
for spirit stones again.
Maybe I should go alone.
Won't you tell Master?
(Forbidden Forest, Yunhua Sect)
(This is the Forbidden Forest?)
(Our Yunhua Sect)
(actually has such a place?)
It's fine.
Those are just
some demonic beasts
who like to scare the disciples.
A spiritual tool here.
Who are you?
Why are you in our
Forbidden Forest?
(Dark energy is spreading.)
(A dark cultivator.)
(What do I do?)
(With my petty spiritual energy...)
(Stay calm. Keep him occupied.)
Formation activation.
Just this?
Scared now, aren't you?
Surrender now.
(Oh no, I've met the real deal.)
Don't get cocky.
Just you wait.
I'll call Master and martial uncle.
How dare
you dark cultivator cause trouble here?
I don't have time for your games.
Wait.
Aren't you scared
I'll call reinforcements?
Listen.
People from our sect
are extremely powerful.
What reinforcements?
Enough blabbering.
It's you?
See?
Here's my reinforcement.
You're finished.
Don't leave me alone.
Wait.
Master.
(Master Qing Yuan, Yunhua Sect)
Don't panic.
Where's your composure?
What happened?
The Forbidden Forest...
What about it?
When I delivered medicine,
I found
someone there.
Did they discover anything?
I'm not sure.
They've even
set up a barrier there.
Master.
We can't let anyone
discover our secret.
Where did they go?
Where are they?
So fast?
Ouch!
This...
This barrier...
Sorry.
I didn't know it was you.
A-Are you okay?
You're amazing.
Right,
you're also investigating
the Longgu Pills
because of the Nascent Soul Elder?
And to catch the dark cultivator.
W-Where is that dark cultivator?
He escaped.
Did he set up
this barrier
to trap us?
I set up this barrier.
You did this?
So you did it to trap
that dark cultivator?
I see.
You're amazing.
I've never seen
such a powerful barrier.
You saved my life.
Sect Leader.
You did
something strange
to earn spirit stones again?
You look ridiculous.
Senior Brother.
Now's not the time for this.
What's with this barrier?
I just arrived myself.
Impressive.
Liuguang Sect's techniques.
That dark cultivator is named Jiusu.
On March 3rd, he killed
15 rogue cultivators
at Yingzhou's Feling Pier.
On March 9th,
he killed 30 disciples of Pingzhou's
Jinxiu Sect.
Scared already?
Who's scared?
I'm a disciple of the Yunhua Sect.
We vanquish demons and evil
and fear nothing...
(Spiritual energy.)
I thought you weren't scared.
I-I'm not scared.
I just got startled
by that sound.
Let go, then.
(Pei Huai, Master of Yunhua Sect's Wuyang Peak)
Someone from
the Liuguang Sect came
and set up barriers.
I'm afraid something went wrong
in the Forbidden Forest.
You brat.
What happened to your face?
You look just the same.
I'll teach you a lesson.
Senior Wang Tong.
Come back.
Pei Huai.
Wang Tong and I will stay here.
Go back with Qing Yuan first.
Understood.
Talking back?
If it's
so dangerous in there,
what will happen to her?
"Her"?
Ling Hui.
Who's in there?
Kong Hou said
there were drug transactions
in the Forbidden Forest
and insisted on
investigating it herself.
Kong Hou is in there?
That's right.
You Liuguang Sect old fools!
Your Luanfeng Peak is up to something.
Don't drag my disciple into this.
If so much
as a single hair on her head is harmed,
I'll pluck every strand of hair
from every member
of Liuguang Sect
and burn your sect
to ashes.
(Zhong Xi's barrier)
(is so hard to break.)
What do we do?
What if he breaks through?
Will you step up?
I'll help you.
Hide if you want to help.
Got it.
It seems
we can't avoid
this battle.
The world seeks to be carefree,
yet you seek to fight.
Do you really see yourself
as a slayer of evils?
No more chitchat.
You're not getting away today.
A cultivator from Luanfeng Peak
is truly extraordinary.
Impressive.
Master.
Let's talk this out.
If you want to live,
come back to Liuguang Sect with me.
This is the dark poison
I've accumulated.
It clashes
with your spiritual energy.
If you activate your spiritual energy,
it'll destroy your spiritual core.
The faster you circulate your energy,
the sooner you die.
How come I can suddenly
use a spiritual tool?
Was it because...
You wretched girl, how dare you
sneak-attack me?
What's wrong?
You sneak-attacked him.
Why can't I do the same to you?
I'll teach you a lesson.
Boost spiritual energy
with heart's blood?
You're truly courting death.
If I can kill you,
death would be worth it.
♪Roaming with the wind♪
♪Wandering about♪
♪A final ember of warmth abides♪
♪Absurd plots unfold♪
♪Mere spectators♪
♪Footprints left on shores♪
♪Fickle kisses burn♪
♪Withering in an instant♪
♪Lanterns glow, depicting her grace♪
♪Like rusted locks♪
♪Chaining our memories♪
♪Only scars remain♪
♪Breaking from worldly desires♪
♪Dreams shattered, but reality rolls on♪
♪Letting down my guard,
drowning in the perilous love♪
♪You stole my heart♪
♪Vows scatter with the air♪
♪All the wounds will heal with care♪
♪Love is mystery♪
♪So be it♪
♪She blazes uncontrolled♪
♪A sickness of the soul♪
♪Cold nights take their toll♪
♪So be it♪
♪All efforts go unrewarded♪
♪Breaking from worldly desires♪
♪Dreams shattered, but reality rolls on♪
♪Letting down my guard,
drowning in the perilous love♪
♪You stole my heart♪
♪Vows scatter with the air♪
♪All the wounds will heal with care♪
♪So be it♪